Can't focus. My body is still puzzled about what to do.
集中できてないな　まだ体が迷っているんだ
Shuuchuu dekitenaina mada karada ga mayotteirunda
I'm trembling. I can't stop even if I try to control myself.
震えていたんじゃ　コントロールしたってブレるんだ
Furueteitanja kontoroorushitatte burerunda
Although neither sun nor moon are on my side,
ツキ
太陽も勝負運もなんも完全にこっち向いていないが
Taiyou mo tsuki mo nanmo kanzen ni kocchi muiteinaiga
"I've no choice but to try,"
「やるしかないんだ」
Yarushikanainda
Those were the words I muttered to myself.
言い聞かせるようにそうつぶやいた
Iikikaseruyouni sotto tsubuyaita
The odds aren't on my side, but running way'd be gutless.
状況は悪いが　ただ逃げ出すんじゃ根性ないなぁ
Joukyou wa waruiga tada nigedasunja konjou nainaa
Even if I can't see the future, I'll just have to win it over with courage.
展望はないが　度胸でクリアするしかないや
Tenbou wa naiga dokyou de kuria suru shika naiya
Need to keep distance from the target as I hold myself back.
衝動は抑えたままターゲットとの間隔探れ
Shoudou wa osaetamama taagetto to no kankaku sagure
All that's needed for victory is pride to win.
必要なもんは勝つプライド
Hitsuyou na mon wa katsu puraido
Will we celebrate with the wine of victory
味わうのは勝利の美酒か
Ajiwau nowa shouri no bishu ka
Or'll we end up kissing their feet in defeat?
それとも敗北の苦汁か
Soretomo haiboku no kujuu ka
There are two outcomes to everything.
そう　すべては2つに1つ
Sou subete wa futatsu ni hitotsu
I want to control destiny.
操りたい運命の糸
Ayatsuritai unmei no ito
I need to seize the golden opportunity with my hands.
絶好のゴールデンタイム　この手で掴め
Zekkou no goorudentaimu kono te de tsukame
I'll finish it up with my best poker face,
渾身のポーカーフェイス　キメて仕掛けるよ
Konshin no pookaafeisu kimete shikakeruyo
And drag them into a world of illusions.
イリュージョンの世界へ引きずり込んで
Iryuujon no sekai e hikizurikonde
I'll find my way out of this endless pressure game,
際限無いプレッシャーゲーム　スルリと抜けて
Saigennai puresshaageemu sururito nukete
And leap over the borderline of honor.
栄光のボーダーライン　飛び越えるために
Eikou no boodaarain tobikoeru tameni
How many? What'll I need to sacrifice to make it happen?
ハウメニー？　どれくらいの代償がいる？
Haumenii? Dorekurai no daishou ga iru?
What is the one thing I don't want to let go?
手放したくないもんはどれ？
Tebanashitakunai mon wa dore?
Hey, where the hell are you taking us?
一体どこに…
乗りな
Get in.
This is...
ここは
Military Headquarters?!
軍司令部どういうこと
What does this mean?!
Hey.
お前ら汚いんだよ
You guys are filthy.
I wouldn't have dreamed the Homunculi's hideout was under Headquarters...
人造人間の根城が
司令部の地下深くにあったなんて
So it means that the army is also associated with them, not just the Führer President.
大総統だけじゃなく
軍自体も関係してたってことか
But I've got something good to tell you, too.
だがな悪い話ばかりでもないぞ
Really?! You really found my body?!
本当本当に僕の体が
Yeah.
Although you told me,
"You're not my soul, so I can't come with you."
「君は 僕の魂じゃないから一緒に行けない」
って言われたけどな
Great, so my body still exists!
そうか体はあるんだ
Awesome! Awesome!
よしよし
Okay!
よしっと
This just means we're one step closer to our goal.
オレたちまた一歩目的に近づいたってわけだ
Hey, why do you still have that cat?
なぜその白黒猫がいる
Oh, her?
これ実はここに…
Actually, inside of me, there's...
What?!
んだとあの豆女が
That midget?!
兄さん声がでかい
Brother! Stop being so loud!
っていうか早くパンツはきなよ
Hurry and put your underwear on!
What are you guys doing?! Hurry up!
何やってんだ早くしろ
No!!!
いやん
Geez, why the hell did you have to bring her?
ったく
なんでそんなヤツ連れてきたんだよ
しょうがないじゃないか
There was no other choice. She's injured.
ケガしてるんだよ
Hey!
I'm leaving the rest to Wrath. Go in.
あとのことはラースに任せてある
入りな
Wrath?
ラース
Wrath...
大総統キングブラッドレイ
Führer President King Bradley?!
Colonel!
大佐
何があった
What the hell happened?
いろいろあったぞ
Quite a bit.
Sergeant Fuery was transferred to the South, Warrant Officer Falman to the North,
フュリー曹長は南
ファルマン准尉は北
and Second Lieutenant Breda to the West.
ブレダ少尉は西へ飛ばされた
And Lieutenant Hawkeye is going to be an assistant to the Führer President.
ホークアイ中尉は大総統付き補佐だそうだ
What the hell...
なんだそりゃ
That's no more than taking hostages.
体のいい人質じゃねぇか
Have a seat.
座りたまえ
Right now, it's just us and the Führer President in this room.
今この部屋には
オレたちと大総統だけ
And he only has one weapon; a sword.
武器は剣一本のみ
Yet, he's still confident he can beat all three of us?
それでも勝てる自信があるというのか
大総統
Führer President!
以前オレが入院したとき
You came to visit me in the hospital once, right?
見舞いに来てくれましたね
I was completely fooled.
まんまとだまされました
"Don't meddle in things.
Think of the entire army as your enemy."
「首を突っ込むな軍内部すべて敵だと思え」
そう命じたはずだよ
That's what I told you.
君たちは我々にとって貴重な人材だ
You are all important to us.
余計なことは知らんでいい
You don't need to know about the minor details,
but behave until the time comes.
ただ時が来るまでおとなしくしていろ
As long as you keep that promise, we won't harm you.
そうすれば悪いようにはせん
And when that time comes, what'll happen to the civilians who aren't "human sacrifices" like us?
そのときが来たら
オレたち「人柱」と呼ばれる者以外の一般人は
どうなるんですか
I just told you. You don't need to know the minor details,
余計なことは知らんでいいと言ったはずだ
Fullmetal Alchemist.
鋼の錬金術師
"Fullmetal Alchemist", eh?
鋼の錬金術師か…
元の体に戻るために軍の狗になる道を選んだ
I chose to become a dog of the military in order to get my body back.
But the State Alchemist Institution itself was probably created to pick out these sacrifices.
だが国家錬金術師制度自体が
おそらく人柱とやらを選ぶためのもの
If I'm going to be used by you guys again on top of that...
このうえ更に
あんたたちに利用されるというなら…
I quit my job as a State Alchemist!
オレは国家錬金術師をやめる
Your proof of being a dog is covered in blood.
狗の証し血にまみれておるわ
Whatever you guys are planning, I'll put an end to it.
あんたたちの企みも
それがなんであれ
必ず頓挫させてやる
I'll tell the other alchemists, and...
ほかの術師たちに言いふらして
そして…
なんといったかなあの娘
What was her name again?
Oh, that's right. Winry Rockbell.
そう ウィンリィ·ロックベル
Born in Resembool.
リゼンブール生まれ
A childhood friend of yours
and someone who is practically family.
君たちの幼なじみで家族にも等しい存在
A skilled automail mechanic.
腕利きの機械鎧技師
She currently works at Rush Valley,
and she's loved by her customers and friends.
今はラッシュバレーで働き
客にも仲間にも恵まれている
She's a good, obedient girl.
素直ないい子だ
Lay a finger on her and see what happens! People around her, too!
あいつに手を出すな
周りの人たちにもだ
So, what are you going to do?
でどうするね
If you still want to quit, then I'll cut her down.
いらんと言うなら切って捨てるが
Excellent.
よろしい
Excuse me...
あの…
We get the idea.
話はだいたい分かりました
So, umm...
それで その…
Like before, please let us continue to search for clues
for getting our bodies back while being under surveillance.
今までどおりそちらの監視下にいるかわりに
元の体に戻る旅を
僕らの旅を続けさせてください
Please.
お願いします
Very well.
かまわんよ
As long as you don't interfere with our plan.
余計なことさえしなければね
What will you do, Colonel Mustang?
マスタング大佐はどうする
まさか軍をやめるなどと言いださんだろうな
You're not going to tell me that you plan to resign from the military too, are you?
Let's see... even if I became a dog of the military, I'd rather not become a loser.
そうですね飼い犬になっても
負け犬になるのは耐えられませんな
何より私の野望のために
Either way, because of my ambition, I won't be able to take off this uniform or get rid of this. For now, at least.
軍服を脱ぐことも
これを捨てることも
今はできそうにありません
Very well.
よろしい皆下がっていいぞ
You all may leave.
May I ask you one thing, sir?
一つ聞いてよろしいでしょうか閣下
What is it, Colonel?
なんだね大佐
Are you the one who killed Hughes?
ヒューズを殺したのはあなたですか
いや私ではない
No, it was not me.
Then who?
では誰が
You said "one thing", did you not?
一つという約束だ
Please excuse me.
失礼します
Oh. Wait a moment, Alphonse.
待ちたまえアルフォンス君
U-Umm... Is there something...
あの何か…
No, you may leave now.
いや行ってよろしい
危なかった
That was so close!
A sword just went right over my head...
頭の上を剣が…
Oh yeah, Colonel.
そうだ大佐
Money. Lend me some change.
金小銭貸してくれ
What's this all of a sudden?
なんだいきなり…
Don't worry about it!
いいから
けっシケてやがんなぁ
Man, this is all you got?
チンピラか君は
What are you, a thief?!
Oh well.
まあいいやじゃあな
Later!
H-Hey!
Sorry, Colonel!
ごめん大佐
あとでいろいろ報告する
We'll report everything later!
What in the world are they up to?
なんだ一体
Oh no, the Lieutenant!
いかん中尉が
Lieute-
中尉…
Is something the matter, Colonel?
いかがなされました大佐
You don't look very well.
顔色が悪いですぞ
Can you blame me for feeling sick after seeing a musclehead when I was expecting to see a woman?
女性との待ち合わせ場所に
筋肉ヒゲダルマが立ってて
血色よくなる男がいるか…
Colonel!
大佐
Lieutenant.
中尉
ご無事でしたか
Is everything okay?
Oh, my apologies.
すみません
Lieutenant Hawkeye, just returning from the restroom, sir.
ホークアイ中尉
ただいまお手洗いから戻りました
I accepted Major Armstrong's kindness and had him take my place for a short time.
アームストロング少佐のご好意に甘え
少しの間 交代を
Thank you, Major.
ありがとうございました少佐
なんのなんの
No problem at all.
You didn't run away?
逃げなかったのか
Who's the one who told me
to never give up no matter what?
何があってもあきらめるなと言ったのは
どこのどなたですか
Don't regret later that you didn't run away, Lieutenant.
あとで逃げた方がマシだった
なんて言うなよ中尉
Like I will after all this time...
何を今更…
はいもしもし
Hello?
Ed? What's with the sudden call?
エドどうしたの急に
Did you break your automail again?
また機械鎧壊したの
違ぇよ
No!
Hey, are you okay?
お前無事か元気にしてるか
Are you doing well?
Anything new in your life?
変わったことないか
You're not being stalked by anyone, are you?
怪しいヤツにつけられたりとかしてないか
Ed...
エド…
What is it?!
なんだ
You're being creepy.
気色悪い
What did you say?!
んだとこらぁ
だって
I mean, it's rare enough for you to call, and it turns out you're worried about me?
エドが電話してくること自体珍しいのに
おまけに人の心配だなんて
Geez, there's something wrong here.
I bet it's going to snow tonight or something.
やだちょっと何これ
雪降るわ
Hey! Do you have any idea how much I-
てめぇ人がどんだけ…
ありがとね
Hey, thanks.
電話うれしい
I'm happy you called.
ありがとう
Thanks.
S-Sure.
So you're really okay, right?
ほんとに大丈夫なんだな
Got it. Bye.
じゃあな
Good, she was fine...
とりあえず無事だった
こういう必死さが
It's your excitable nature that lets people take advantage of you.
つけ込まれる隙になるんだよな
Ling!
リン
グリードだっつうの
I told you, I'm Greed.
What the hell do you want?!
なんの用だ
Your buddy asked me to give you this.
お前のダチに頼まれた
Ling did?
リンに
This is in Xing's language, huh...
シンの言葉か
What's it say?
なんて書いてあるんだ
I don't know. Can't read it.
知らん読めん
He wants you to give it to the woman waiting for him.
こいつを待ってる女に渡してくれとよ
ランファあとをつけてきて
Lan Fa-
You're not planning on following us and killing her, are you?
その女を殺すとかじゃないだろうな
んなせこいマネするかよ
I'm not that low.
Besides, I don't like fighting girls.
それに女と戦う趣味はねぇ
I don't lie.
オレはうそをつかねぇのを信条にしている
Later. Be sure to give it to her.
じゃあな頼んだぞ
Hey, Ling!
おいリン
I'm Greed.
グリードだ
あれは何者だ
Who the hell was that?
この国を疲弊させてまで
What reason did he have to start the civil war
when it would ruin this country?
内乱を起こす必要がなぜあった…
誰だ
Who is it?
誰か そこにいるのか
Is someone up there?
ケガをしているのか
You're injured.
下りてきてくれないか
Could you come down?
外の状況が知りたい
I'd like to know what's going on outside.
大丈夫だ
It's fine; the guard won't be coming again for a while.
しばらく見回りも来ない
それに私は医者だ
I'm also a doctor. I'll tend your wounds.
君のケガも見よう
イシュヴァール人か
An Ishbalan, huh?
That scar on your forehead...
その額の傷…
まさかお前がスカー
Don't tell me... You're Scar?!
Who the hell are you?
貴様は何者だ
ここで何をしている
What are you doing here?
Oh, God!
神よ
I'm...
私も 私もイシュヴァール殲滅に加担した
I'm also an alchemist who assisted in the Ishbal Extermination!
錬金術師だ
大丈夫だ命に別状はない
She'll be fine. Nothing life-threatening.
She'll get better as long as she gets some rest.
しばらく安静にしてりゃ治るだろう
Thank goodness.
よかった
よかねぇよ
"Thank goodness" my ass!
勝手に患者増やしやがって
Giving me more patients by the day!
ベッドとソファー 占拠されて
Both my bed and sofa are occupied!
今日からオレはどこに寝りゃいいんだ
Where the hell am I supposed to sleep, huh?!
ごめんなさいごめんなさい
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Besides, two patients in my house at once?!
Alphonse.
アルフォンス
ランファン
Lan Fan!
ダメだよまだ寝てなきゃ
You shouldn't be up!
Is... Is the young master not with you?
若は若は一緒じゃないのか
I-It's fine. He's alive.
だ大丈夫生きてる
I have a message from him.
伝言を預かってきた
ランファン
Lan Fan?
賢者の…
He says... He says he's obtained a philosopher's stone...
賢者の石を手に入れたと…
With this, our clan is...
これで我が一族は…
That's right! I must return to my country immediately and tell my people!
そうだ一刻も早く国に帰って
皆にこのことを知らせねば
Where is he? Where is the young master?
若は若はどこに
なんだなぜ黙っている
What? Why won't you speak?
まさか若の身に何か…
Don't tell me something happened to him!
Answer me, Alphonse!
答えろアルフォンス
若はどこだ
Where is the young master?!
体の調子はどうだグリード
How is your body feeling, Greed?
あんたがラースか
So you're Wrath.
調子はいいぜ
I'm feeling fine.
Did you hear? This body belongs to a prince of Xing.
聞いたか
この体シンの皇子だってよ
He wanted power that would help him become Emperor, and thus accepted me.
皇帝になる力を手に入れたくて
自らオレを受け入れやがった
He's a really interesting guy.
おもしろい野郎だ
Him and I once had a discussion on what it means to be a true king.
真の王とはなんぞやと
その皇子に問答したことがある
He said something like, "A King exists for his people. Without his people, there is no King."
「王は民のためにあるもの
民なくしてはありえない」
などとぬかしおったが…
バカめ欲をかいてすべて失ったではないか
What an idiot. He gave in to greed and lost everything.
Shut up!
やかましい
人間をなめるな
Don't underestimate us humans!
That's how it is.
つうわけよ
He's vigilantly watching for a chance to take over.
こいつ隙あらばオレを乗っ取ろうと
虎視眈々だぜ
He's even planning on taking control of a monster?
化け物すらも飲み込もうというのか
How greedy can these humans get?
どこまでも強欲な人間よ
大総統が人造人間
The Führer President is a Homunculus?!
我が輩は
It's always been my honor to fight for the weak citizens of this country.
この国の弱き人民のために
戦いたいと思っていました
多くの者がそう思い
Many people feel the same,
believe in the military, and sign up.
軍を信じ籍を置いております
And yet, the military itself...
なのにその軍が…
Why not resign?
軍をやめてはどうだ
With your personality, being a soldier will only hurt you.
君の性格では
いてもつらいだけだろう
Sir! This is wrong!
こんな戦いは間違っています閣下
Are you going against military command?!
軍令に背く気か
Whatever! Call for a replacement State Alchemist!
もうよい
代わりの国家錬金術師を呼べ
イシュヴァールで
I ran from battle during Ishbal...
我が輩は戦いから逃げました
...because I thought what the army was doing was wrong.
軍のやり方は間違っている
But instead, I should have fought against it instead of running away.
そう思いながら
ですがその間違っているものとこそ
戦うべきだった
Since then, not a day has passed that I didn't feel ashamed for bending my principles and fleeing.
あれから今日この日まで
信念を曲げ逃げた己を
恥じなかった日はありません
And this time, if the army itself is the battlefield, how can I run away again?
今また軍が戦場というのなら
我が輩一人
どうしてしっぽを巻いて
逃げられましょうか
大佐はこれからどうなさるのですか
What are you going to do now, Colonel?
I told the Führer President I wouldn't quit because I still have an ambition.
大総統には野望があるから
まだやめんと言ってやった
大総統が自ら人造人間であることを
The fact the Führer President revealed he's a Homunculus means that even if he was to be defeated,
私に明かしたということは
自分を倒したとしても
there's still someone else in the shadows.
まだ後ろがいると暗示したということだ
試されている光栄じゃないか
I'm being tested.
Don't you think that's an honor?
You're being pretty calm about this.
意外と余裕ですね
I don't know if I'd say that.
どうかな
It was the same when I fought that other Homunculus, Lust, but...
ただラストとかいう人造人間と
戦ったときもそうだったが
「兵器だ化け物だ」といわれる自分が
Although people accuse me of being a "weapon" and a "monster", when fighting against real monsters...
本物の化け物と戦っているときにこそ
己がただの人間であることを実感できるよ
...I truly feel as though I'm nothing but an ordinary human.
I see.
そうか
若は自ら賢者の石を受け入れたのか
So the young master took in the stone.
ごめん
Sorry.
僕たちが止めていれば…
If only we had been able to stop him...
謝る必要はない
You don't need to apologize.
I am only mad at myself for not being able to fulfill my duty as a bodyguard.
護衛の役目を果たせなかった自分に
腹が立っているのだ
若は若はまだ
So...
So the young master is still inside this Greed person, right?
そのグリードというヤツの中にいるんだな
Alphonse, I want a replacement arm. And quick.
アルフォンス
腕が欲しい今すぐに
そんなすぐったって…
But... it'll take some time...
Please introduce me to an automail mechanic! Please!
機械鎧技師を紹介してくれ頼む
分かった
Okay.
I will soon.
なるべく早く紹介するよ
でもその前に体力をつけないと
But you have to get better before I do that.
Let's get you something to eat from Dr. Nox...
ノックス先生にご飯をもらって…
もう起きて大丈夫なの
You can get up now?
Let's see... was your name May Chan?
えっとメイ·チャンだっけ
メイ
May?!
何
What?!
さすがヤオ家の番犬
As expected of the Yao Clan's watchdog.
And you're... the Chan Clan's successor.
そういうお前はチャンの後継
Indeed.
いかにも
Wait... um...
I'm the 17th Princess of Xing, May Chan.
（えっとあの…）
第１７皇女メイ·チャンです
この国に来たということは
If you're here in this country, it means... you're after immortality, as well.
狙いは不老不死
I'll never let you and your clan have it!
あなたたちにだけは渡しません
You won't even be able to find it!
お前はたどりつくことすらできん
Hang on!
ちょっと待ってよ
なんだか知らないけど
I don't really get it, but let's play nice!
ケンカはやめてって
人の国の事情に…
Don't interfere with our country's affairs!
口を出さないでください
Don't underestimate me just because I'm injured.
手負いだからといってなめるなよ
そのセリフそのままお返しします
Same to you!
何やっとんじゃこら
What the hell are you two doing?!
Patients should be asleep in bed!
病人はおとなしく寝てろ
ひ人の国の事情に…
Don't interfere with our country's...
てめぇの国の事情なんざ
Hell if I care about your country's affairs, moron!
知るかバカ野郎
ったく
Geez!
病人は万国共通で病人だ
Patients are patients, no matter what country they're in!
これ以上うちを散らかしてくれるってのか
You're planning on messing up my house even more?
Hey...
医者の家から
You've heard about cases where unknown pathogens mysteriously appear in a doctor's house and kill everyone...
未知の病原菌が出て全員死亡
...right?!
あるよなぁ
ほんとに散らかり放題だ
This place really is a mess.
誰か片づけてくれる人はいないのかな
Doesn't he have anyone to clean for him?
Doctor, look.
先生これ
Oh, so that's where it was.
こんな所にあったか
Wait! Isn't this a picture of your family?!
ちょっ…
家族の写真じゃないんですか
It's my divorced wife and my son.
別れた女房と息子だ
What?
なんだよオレのものをどうしようが
I'm free to do whatever I want with my stuff!
オレの勝手だろうが
片づけたらコーヒーでも飲んでけ
Have a cup of coffee after this is all cleaned up.
来てくれて助かったわ
I'm so glad you came!
何しろこの有様でしょ
Seriously, look at this.
I was at a loss about what to do.
どうしようか途方に暮れてたとこなの
Huh? Now that I think about it, I can use alchemy again.
あれそういや術が使えてる
Very nice work! This is all for the repairs.
いやお疲れさまでした
これで修復はすべて完了です
But seriously, State Alchemists are something else.
しかしさすがは国家錬金術師
そこいらの術師とは格が違いますなぁ
On a totally different level from other alchemists.
実は午前中近場の錬金術師に
The thing is, we asked nearby alchemists to help us this morning.
復旧を手伝ってもらったんですが
They were completely useless.
そいつらの使えないことときたら
もう…
自信満々で現場に入っておきながら
They came to the scene all full of themselves, and as soon as they were getting started, they told us it wasn't working.
いざ始めたら術が使えないってなぁ
午前中…
In the morning...
That's around the time we were underground.
オレたちが地下にいたころか
錬金術師さん
Mr. Alchemist!
Thanks!
ありがとう
Thanks.
エンヴィーの言ったことを
Can I really believe what Envy said?
本当に信じていいのか
That those people are only made of energy, without a body or a soul...
あれが肉体も精神もない
ただのエネルギー体だって…
しっかりしろ
Pull yourself together! Think about the future, not the past!
これから先のことを考えるんだ
あのとき
But at that time, other alchemists aside from Al and I were unable to use alchemy.
オレとアルだけじゃなく
ほかの術師たちも錬金術が使えなくなっていた
But that midget and Scar could.
でもあの豆女とスカーは使うことができた
どういうことだ
What does this mean?
オレたちのとは違う錬金術
Alchemy that's different from ours...
If I could find out the secret behind it,
その秘密を聞き出せば…
there may be a way to get Al's body back and fight against that geezer without using a philosopher's stone...
あるいは賢者の石を使わなくても
アルの体を取り戻し
あのヒゲ野郎に対抗することが…
I have to return this to the Lieutenant.
これ中尉に返さなきゃ
Even if we part and meet again, I want to meet at this place.
Megurimeguttemo mata koko de aitai
Then we'll hold hands to ensure we'll never be separated again.
Hagurenaiyouni kono te wo tsunagunda
We used to talk all night until the sun rose,
Asahi ga noboru made katariattane
And held hands till the sun went under the horizon.
Yuuhi ga shizumu made tsunaida te
Let's walk together like this forever, like light and shadow.
Kouyatte asu mo asatte mo tomo ni ayumou hikari to kage
Right now I'm curios what you're holding inside
Kimi wa sono mune ni nani wo kakae
And what kind of world you've been living in.
Donna sekai ni itandarou ima omouyo
I stand in the city, staring off into space with lonely eyes.
Samishige ni mitsumeru machi no naka de
I can't find warmth on my own.
Nukumori wa hitori ja mitsukaranakute
By meeting you, I realized
Ai ga konnani tsuyosa ni narukoto
How much strength love could give me.
Shittanda kimi ni deaete hajimete
Even if we part and meet again, I want to meet at this place.
Megurimeguttemo mata koko de aitai
Hagurenaiyouni kono te wo tsunagunda
Then we'll hold hands to ensure we'll never be separated again.
Hitori ja nemurenai yume wa mirenaikara
I can't sleep by myself, 'cause I can't dream without you.
So take me to a place where uncertainty can't reach us
Donna fuan mo todokanai tokoro e
And let us bring light to the night sky with no stars.
Hoshi no yoru mo terashitsuzukeyou
I can't sleep by myself, 'cause I can't dream without you.
Hitori ja nemurenai yume wa mirenaikara
So take me to a place where uncertainty can't reach us
Donna fuan mo todokanai tokoro e
If I wish for a dream that can't be reached on my own,
Hitori ja kanawanai yume wo egaitanara
私はヤツらに協力させられてきた
PLACEHOLDER
They made me help them.
With the two of us, we can make it come true.
Kimi to futari de kanaeni yukunda
PLACEHOLDER
I created philosopher's stones and took the lives of many Ishbalans.
賢者の石を作り
多くのイシュヴァール人の命を奪った
You and I are a pair; we can't achieve happiness without each other.
Kimi to hanbun hitotsu no shiawase
PLACEHOLDER
And now, I'm on the verge of being forced to work on an experiment that would cause more deaths.
そして今私は
更に多くの犠牲を出すであろう
実験に協力させられようとしている
So...
だからだから頼む
So please, I'm begging you! Kill me!
私を殺してくれ今ここで
Right here, right now!
I'm going to get back at them with death!
私は死をもってヤツらに一矢報いる
Right now, in my eyes, you appear as God...
私には君が神のように見える…
You haven't told me everything about Ishbal yet!
まだイシュヴァールの話を
すべて聞いていないぞ
What the hell did you bastards do there?!
貴様らあの地で何をやった
Tell me everything, Marcoh!
すべて話せマルコー
この右手が貴様を破壊せぬうちに
Before my right hand destroys you!!!
暴力
Force. Never-ending violence.
日本語字幕仕上げ：XIAOBIN
それはやむことのない蹂躙
The earth is drowned in blood.
大地は赤い血を吸わされ
漫遊字幕組
http://popgo.net/bbs
The air is choked with the stench of burnt flesh.
大気は焼けた肉のにおいにむせ返る
イシュヴァール
Ishbal...
それは忌まわしき記憶
A detestable memory.
次回　鋼の錬金術師
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
FULLMETALALCHEMIST
Episode 30, The Ishvalan War of Extermination.
第30話「イシュバァール殲滅戦」
真実を語る
I will recite the truth.
Although I'm the only one left.
たとえ一人になっても